No, Jas.
Yew. Live.
Yes, sir.
So you're related to the picture book?
Yes, yes.
Yes, please.
Here we go.
Nice to meet you.
We're like people who are busy with computers and sns, like in a coffee shop or something.
Like people with free time on their hands. Good evening.
Today it's a little cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy, cloudy...
I don't want to be in the middle of a cloudy sky, but...
I don't want to be in the middle of the sky and have a little flicker, but how is everyone doing today?
So, as you can see, the shift is ready, so here's the dumpling pandey!
Yoo-hoo!
Yes!
I'd like to start again with the mainstay of the company...
I'd like to start again with the mainstay of the group.
First of all, let's begin.
Let's begin.
I'm under a lot of pressure from the Surgeon General...
What should I do?
What shall I do?
Gargle! Gargling?
You've been gargling since the show started?
Oh no...
I can't think of anything.
Oh, by the way...
You know, the other day, Sawapon...
Put this in your ear
It's easy to get warm.
You know those health products that warm your ears?
And he said, "That's a good idea.
And I was under the impression that it would help me sleep better, so I went to the pharmacy right there and bought some ear-pumps.
So I went to the pharmacy right there and told them I had some warm ones that you could pop in your ears.
And they said, "Good idea!
Well, it wasn't the same manufacturer.
I think it was that air pod thing, and then I put that little thing from Hokkaido inside.
And when it got warm, I did it.
How was it?
It had no effect.
What?
Me...
You know, when I try to sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, sleep, I get excited.
That's true.
Wow!
It's like...
It's like, "Oh, my God, time's over.
Oh, no...
It's only about 20 minutes.
It was surprisingly short.
So short.
What the hell, one more time...
Even if I let him out one more time, he'd still come back in.
But it was fun.
It's nice, isn't it?
It's like when you warm up your ears, you don't have that experience anymore.
That's right.
I don't know if it helped.
I don't know.
Maybe it's a relaxing effect.
Do fishermen do that too, by the way?
I use it too.
What's that?
That's crazy!
Does that mean it's selling really well?
It seems to be selling well.
I see.
When I'm on the move, like before a concert...
It's true, but it's blocked up, so there's not much sound coming in.
That's right.
That's also a nice touch.
I use it on airplanes and bullet trains.
On the move
Heh.
I thought I'd get a hold of my surf bone and complain about it.
I didn't really think it'd be a good idea.
I'm glad.
But there's a lot going on.
There's a lot going on.
Thank you.
One more time.
One more time
Well, well, well, I'm getting used to that switch.
Yes, you're right.
At first, I thought I'd put it in, but then it fell out.
Darn it.
You've got to be kidding me.
That's what's happening.
That's for sure.
I got excited.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm getting more and more spot-on.
I'm getting better at spotting.
I'd like to invite you all, if you don't mind, to warm up your ears a little bit.If you'd like to warm up your ears a little, I'd recommend it.
I highly recommend it!
Well, well, well...
First of all...
Well...
Well, today, be gentle.
Yes.
What's the date tomorrow?
Let me tell you something.
Yes, sir.
Tomorrow is Friday, June 16th.
June 16th
Mugitoro Day
Mugitoro (barley and tuna)
Like June 16th
Mugitoro Day and
barley and grated yam
Do you eat barley grated yam?
What is barley grated yam?
I love it.
By the way, what is barley grated yam?
It's barley rice with grated yam.
It's delicious.
You know...
That's it, isn't it?
When you go to Sendai or something...
Beef tongue.
Yes, yes, yes.
But...
That yam...
Looks delicious
Tea, soy sauce, sake, mirin, egg, miso...
Neri?
Sorry
It's short for green onion and green laver.
"Neri" for leeks and green onions.
Neri for short.
It's so strong!
Everyone, use it!
He looks like he's really good at martial arts!
Neri (scallion)
Negi (green onion), Aonori (green laver), etc. are sometimes added
The seasoning varies from region to region.
In fact, this barley rice has barley in it, of course.
Barley is rich in vitamins and minerals, which are often lost through perspiration.
It's also an excellent food for preventing summer fatigue.
Barley rice is delicious, isn't it?
It's not easy to find unless it's a beef tongue set meal.
I'm sure it's just a simple dish.
Well, that's why I'm here.
It's like this. Wise words! Let's say it!
This is a great quote!
First of all, I'd like to introduce a quote by a famous film director, Woody Allen.
There is a famous movie director, Woody Allen, who is quite famous.
He is a famous film director, Woody Allen.
He looks very fashionable, doesn't he?
He often says interesting quotes.
I'd like you to listen to it.
May I? To fall in love is to suffer.
If you don't want to suffer, don't fall in love. But if you do, you will suffer again because you are not in love.
So you end up falling in love!
That's what I mean!
We all do!
Right! After all...
I see.
Well...
Love... You all do it, don't you?
That's right.
For example, when you were little...
You had your first love when you were little.
What did you do?
Did you confess it?
No!
But my first love was in junior high.
Whaaaat!
No way! What? Huh? Huh? Huh? Are you in middle school? What? Not elementary school?
What? What? Junior high, right? Huh? So you weren't in love in elementary school?
Yes. Wow, you're gonna suffer again.
Suffer. Yeah, what's wrong?
Yes, that's right.
And in junior high school... elementary school...
I suddenly started to have feelings for a girl I used to hang out with at lunchtime.
Aah! It's a wake-up call!
Aah!
Wake up! I'm awake!
That's right. I'm awake.
I see.
So we were in the same class in junior high school, and we were next to each other.
And we were in the same class in junior high school, and we were next to each other, and I was like, "I like you.
What? What? That's how you confessed your love to him?
I like you, I like you, I like you.
Then I started thinking about you... but maybe I'm a junior high schooler? That's how I confessed.
Oh! Around that time? I did.
And what happened then?
No!
I'm glad. We tied the knot.
It's a good story. But then Nakajima...
I didn't really understand love. I didn't know what was right.I really don't know what love is. I don't know what the right answer is.
In the end, we broke up without going anywhere.
When you're in junior high school, you don't have any money.
I didn't know what to do. But after school...
But after school, we'd stay in the classroom and talk.
That's about it.
What's going on?
I love it.
Hey!
Something like that...
I wonder if she's watching now.
Shame, shame, shame.
Please email me!
I'll make sure to report her real name
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not easy... to confess.
It seems so easy.
But it's hard.
The thing I fear the most as a young man...
By confessing...
After you've made friends with someone
But if you're afraid of awkwardness...
If you're afraid of that, you'll fall into the darkness.
When you're young
When you're young, it's like you're in a fog.
Blah, blah, blah.
Boo-hoo!
Star Boss
I hear it's like that. By the way, do you remember if dumpling buns are your first love or not? I probably didn't have the concept of first love. I just liked or disliked him as a person.
But now that I think about it, maybe it was in kindergarten, or maybe it was a boy I was close to for a long time, but now that I think about it, I think I probably liked him.
First love. Actually, I think it was my first love.
First love. It was your first love.
What was she like? We were playing. With each other?
He doesn't say he likes you, but he's the type of boy who would make a move on a girl he likes.
He's always messing with me. Like, flipping up my skirt.
It's one of the traditional arts I miss. Skirt flipping.
And I'd tell him to stop, and he'd get mad at me, and I'd tell him to stop, but he'd do it the most because he was the one who was playing with the boys.
I see... I see...
I see... I like that...
It's a great story, Master.
That was my first love.
My first love was probably in kindergarten.
That was quick. It's like that.
You just don't remember?
I don't know...
I mean, me, I think it was just some girl in the neighborhood that I got along with.
I think it was a girl in the neighborhood that I became friends with, but I still remember her.
She said she was moving to Iwatsuki in Saitama.
And on the day of the move, she said, "Okay, bye," and we drove off in the car and said bye-bye like in a drama.
He said bye bye in the car like in a drama.
Dad took me to Iwatsuki.
But we got stuck in a traffic jam and came back.
It was so crowded, it was like an emotional battle.
You can't do this. It'll be tomorrow.
Shall we stop?
He's floundering.
But I think we were probably classmates.
Probably the same age as me.
I'm sure he's probably got a grandson or something... but I'm not going to cut him off... but by the way, there's one more thing he said...
I'd like you to read this one, Mr. Sawapon, who loves f1.
Honda is a global company that is proud of its success in both cars and motorcycles and has become the Honda of the world, and is famous for Honda cars.
Mr. Soichiro Honda is famous as the founder of Honda, and this time, Mr. Sarpong has written an article about him.
I haven't seen it yet.
It's been a while since I've had a stomach ache.
Yes, I have.
I've heard of him.
But his face is a little... honest.
Then, please do.
I've written it down.
This way, please.
Boober...
You're a grandfather, right?
No, no, no, I wrote a lot.
This robot, this robot, this man... this man...
Buber Shi, one of the charismatic figures in the Japanese economy...
He said, "I'd like to read it.
He said he'd like to read it... and this is the picture of him.
Yes, sir.
I'm not going in! I'm not going in! I'm going in for a lot of things!
1%?
It has to be more than 1%.
Only 1% of the work I've done has been truly successful.
I mean, the other 99%, they're not what you'd call a success.
That's what I mean.
That's the Honda of this world.
That's amazing.
Not bad.
What is he trying to say?
That's right.
What's he trying to say?
Yay!
But yes, the business and the car industry are still in the process of...
The business and the car industry are still in the process of evolving.
Oh, those were the days.
I guess that's what you're saying.
Well, I don't know if that's true.
Yes, that's right.
Please tell me.
I feel like I'm about to talk.
I feel like I'm about to talk.He's about to talk.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, you're not.
You look like an old man dressed up as Superman.
It's Halloween.
For the grandkids.
Don't be silly, Grandpa.
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Well, well, well...
Even the Honda's of the world still
Most of the time, I'm told I'm a failure.
I see...
Yes, yes, yes
Well, well, well...
Thank you very much
And...
You see...
Well...
I also got this photo from Cervon the cat.
Let's go this way first.
I really like standing-only noodles.
I probably eat it at least once a day.
It's cool, isn't it?
This time of year, many restaurants start serving it... but do you know this?
It's a chilled dish, but it has a spoon attached to it, so you can see how it's eaten as chilled tofu.
I'm sure you know this... but it looks delicious.
I'm sure you know this, but this is something I get every summer, and it doesn't look so good, but I think it's better than eating it as is.
I'm sorry, but if it were right here in front of me, I wouldn't say "boo".
I wouldn't have said "boo".
If you hadn't said that, it wouldn't have happened.
I'm thinking that I should do something about the way I look.
There are various tofu-like dishes, but they taste good when mixed together.
It's more delicious when it's mixed with other dishes.
If you break it up, it tastes better when mixed like natto (fermented soybeans).
However, I'm sure there are many people who go to standing-only noodle shops or ramen shops.
Sometimes a terrible thing happens when you try to eat.
The chopsticks don't open at all.
When you feel the force being applied to the chopsticks is too much, that's when you usually find yourself in this situation.
It's called "Negilock", isn't it?
Negilocks are scary!
It's called "Negi-Rock".
That's right.
Negi-rocks.
It's a leek rock.
I've got a lot of these.
I'm sure you'll be able to find them in your distribution list.
It's like this, isn't it?
Negi-Lock
They get stuck in there, don't they?
You know "leek lock"?
It happens frequently.
It's true. And it suddenly locks up when you least expect it.
It's like, "Whoa! For a moment, I thought I was being attacked by some unseen force.
I thought I was being forced to do it by some invisible force.
When I look at my real phone, it's like...
99% of the pictures are of noodles.
It's a picture of noodles. Oh, my God, it's like the other 1% succeeded.
Please don't say that here. I'm sorry, Mr. Soichiro.
I love this area, too. I love the so-called "city" atmosphere.
So I went for a little street style, like this.
It's nice. It's aged well.
It's like it's faded.
I heard they have great miso ramen.
So I said, "Excuse me," and ordered the miso ramen.
And it was only 540 yen!
540 yen!
It was good!
But it took quite a long time to come out.
Even though there weren't that many customers!
I wondered why, but the restaurant was in downtown Asakusa.
Asakusa style.
The customers and the store staff were all into sumo.
Like, "Go, go, go!
They're watching.
That's why they were so absorbed.
I forgot how different downtown culture is.
The customers were on their feet.
It's amazing, isn't it? The downtown area is unique.
It's interesting that you really like sumo.
By the way, when I left the restaurant, I looked up and saw the beautiful Sky Tree.
Like this. Wow, it's so close. So close, so close.
Isn't it amazing?
It's scary or surprising... you know, Tokyo Tower is just standing there in the middle of a building...
It's not so bad... but it's in a residential area...
I wonder what they would do if it collapsed.
If you say it's idealistic, it makes me think of the Sky Tree for a moment...
I'd get a kick out of that.
Can we send out more firemen? Of course.
There's the platform door... and not leaning on it... and not putting up a shield...
I like it.
You should put up a shield.
You don't see many people walking on the platform with a board like this, do you?
I don't see many people like this in the city.
And here's a picture of the staff.
I had an event at CIGA the other day, so I came down to Kyoto via the event.
It was the first time in my life that I went to Kyoto.
I don't really know what I ate.
I still had some time left in Kyoto, so I went to a certain place.
And isn't Gyo-san amazing? There are ninjas!
Japonesian Ninja?
This is Shingo, his partner Shingo, and two back-up dancers.That's Shingo, his partner Shingo, and two of the back-up dancers.
The two back-up dancers have interesting faces.
What's with all the yellow? Are you okay?
What's wrong with your liver?
You look like you have a bad liver.
It's a staff member.
You look a little pale.
But you're a ninja, so I guess you'll be fine.
Japonesian Ninja.
Kyoto was good, right?
It was great.
Did you see it? Somewhat.
I saw it.
I thought it was totally different from Tokyo.
It's different.
There were no air raids during the war, so the streets are still there.
The old streets.
It's a little bit like a natural curve.
That's right.
I'd like to go there for sightseeing next time.
Yes, yes, yes.
Speaking of Nakajima Raiya in Kyoto...
Sauna
What?
Anime?
No, no, no.
Ria Nakajima is a sauna.
A sauna?
I did.
Yes, I did.
In Kyoto.
Wow, it's so tame.
Very austere.
I'd love to go to a place like this.
I've never been to a traditional bathhouse before.
I've never been to a traditional bathhouse before, so I was a little excited.
I'd like to go back and get it in order.
This is nice.
What's this?
It's like an old-fashioned painting.
I don't know.
It's like an advertisement.
And there's a reception desk on a slightly elevated platform.
Bandai Ne
That's right.
That's nice.
I enjoyed the old-fashioned sauna or public bath a little bit.
It's nice.
Nice.
I like this kind of thing.
It was really nice.
I've never been to a sauna, so I don't know.
I've never been to a sauna, so I don't know... but let's say it's a public bath.
You go there and put a towel on first.
You're completely naked, but you don't cover your towel.
Hey, hey, hey!
You go to the bathhouse, go in, wash, and go in.
And then you go in, and you wash up, and then you go in, and then you sit down on one of those yellow chairs or something.
Like a yellow plastic chair.
That, that, that...
You go in there, and you come out, and you come out, and you come out, and it's like a rattle.
You know, it's like a clear refrigerator.
There's coffee milk and fruit milk in it.
I went in and drank it.
I drank it.
It was great.
It's great, isn't it?
I love it.
I'm pretty sure I have coffee milk and milk once in a while.
But sometimes fruit milk...
Yes, there is.
I think there's probably a place like this.
Yes, yes, yes.
Fruit milk is delicious.
Like this.
Drink it.
Gah!
You're wearing it on your hip.
And then I hide it like this, just in case.
That's right.
It's a little awkward to be naked in front.
It's not cool if I'm naked in front.
That's right.
Well...
By the way...
Have you ever been to a sauna?
My master took me to a sauna once.
I didn't know what to expect.
Did you get it right then?
But I felt like my whole body was drained.
Gudane.
So you're in shape.
You mean you're in shape?
I was like, "Let's take a break.
And then I just said, "I'm still a little afraid to go in there by myself.
I haven't tried it yet.
I heard it's good for something.
You've been talking about saunas a lot lately.
We've been talking about it all the time.
Week after week. If you ask me, it's sauna harassment.Week after week, week after week, so if you ask me, this is sauna harassment.
Sauna harassment
I really want you to go once.
I want you to go to Maya Maya because it's a real sauna.
I want you to go.
Let's do it.
The sauna boom is unprecedented.
Let's go with Deville.
Devil's advocate?
Let's go in the Devil's Den.
Oh, my God, me and Saton, we're gonna get naked.
Come on, come on, come on.
Like this.
Like Psi Psi Psi.
Well, that's it.
The live streaming is about to end
And that's that.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
We'll be back next week at the same time.
So...
Thank you very much.
See you all next week.
Bye bye.
Thank you very much.